Guide to the Christian Conference of Asia Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Program Areas / Activities, Series IV
  - Development and Service
    - Administrative Records
      - Correspondence
        - Correspondence re. Health concerns workshops, 1982-1985 (Box 129, Folder 8)
        - Correspondence re. health notes, 1980-1983 (Box 129, Folder 9)
        - Correspondence re. hunger concerns, 1976 (Box 129, Folder 10)
        - Correspondence re. hunger concerns, 1980-1984 (Box 129, Folder 11)
        - Correspondence re. Laos Visit, 3-5 June, 1987 (Box 129, Folder 12)
        - Correspondence re. Liberation Motifs in the Faiths of Asia workshop, 1978-1979 (Box 129, Folder 13)
        - Correspondence re. publications, 1980-1982 (Box 129, Folder 14)
        - Correspondence re. refugees, 1976-1977 (Box 129, Folder 15)
        - Correspondence re. refugees, 1980-1986 (Box 129, Folder 16)
        - Correspondence re. "Values of Human Community" survey paper, 1978 (Box 129, Folder 17)
        - Correspondence re. WCC/CCPD Appropriate Technology, 1976 (Box 129, Folder 18)
        - Correspondence re. WCC/CCPD Appropriate Technology, 1980 (Box 129, Folder 19)
        - Correspondence re. WCC/CCPD Asia Regional Group, 1980-1984 (Box 129, Folder 20)
        - Correspondence re. WCC/CICARWS Asia Regional Group, Resource Sharing, 1984-1985 (Box 129, Folder 21)
        - Correspondence re. WCC Procurement Survey, 1974-1975 (Box 129, Folder 22)
        - Correspondence, Training Institutes, 1982-1988 (Box 129, Folder 23)
        - Correspondence, UNCTAD, 1979 (Box 129, Folder 24)
        - Correspondence, WCC Christian Medical Commission (CMC), 1979-1987 (Box 129, Folder 25)
        - Correspondence, WCC Christian Medical Commission (CMC), 1987 (Box 129, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence by region/country
        - Australia, 1976, 1984 (Box 129, Folder 27)
        - Bangladesh, 1971, 1973 (Box 129, Folder 28)
        - Bangladesh, 1980-1985 (Box 129, Folder 29)
        - Bangladesh, 1986-1991 (Box 129, Folder 30)
        - Burma, 1988-1991 (Box 129, Folder 31)
        - Hong Kong, 1974-1976 (Box 129, Folder 32)
        - India, 1980, 1987 (Box 129, Folder 33)
        - Indonesia, 1977, 1980 (Box 129, Folder 34)
        - Japan, 1987-1994 (Box 129, Folder 35)
        - Korea, incl. Activity News: Newsletter of the NCC in Korea, 1987-1992 (Box 129, Folder 36)
        - Laos, 1980-1993 (Box 130, Folder 1)
        - Malaysia, 1972-1973 (Box 130, Folder 2)
        - Malaysia incl. reports, 1987 (Box 130, Folder 3)
        - Nepal, United Mission to Nepal, 1980-1982 (Box 130, Folder 4)
        - Philippines, 1974-1979 (Box 130, Folder 5)
        - Philippines incl. papers and newsletters, 1986-1997 (Box 130, Folder 6)
        - Philippines, Ecumenical Center for Development Education, 1980 (Box 130, Folder 7)
        - Singapore (Institute for the Study of Religions and Society), 1980 (Box 130, Folder 8)
        - Sri Lanka, 1974-1977, 1980-1981 (Box 130, Folder 9)
          includes photographs
        - Sri Lanka, 1987-1992 (Box 130, Folder 10)
        - Taiwan, 1977-1985 (Box 130, Folder 11)
        - Thailand, 1974-1977, 1979-1986 (Box 130, Folder 12)
        - Thailand, Church of Christ in Thailand, 1994-1995 (Box 130, Folder 13)
        - Thailand projects (1 of 2), 1986-1993 (Box 130, Folder 14)
        - Thailand projects (2 of 2), 1986-1993 (Box 130, Folder 15)
        - Other countries outside Asia, 1980-1985 (Box 130, Folder 16)
      - Programme
        - ACWC Working Committee meeting minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 179, Folder 19)
        - Asia Partnership for Human Development correspondence and reports, 1975-1976 (Box 130, Folder 17)
        - Asia Resource Sharing Group, correspondence and meeting materials, 1987-1990 (Box 130, Folder 18)
        - Asia Sunday, 1995-1997 (Box 130, Folder 19)
        - CCA reports, proposals and programmes (1 of 3), 1984-1992 (Box 130, Folder 20)
        - CCA reports, proposals and programmes (2 of 3), 1984-1992 (Box 130, Folder 21)
        - CCA reports, proposals and programmes (3 of 3), 1984-1992 (Box 130, Folder 22)
        - CCA UN/ESCAP, 1986-1990 (Box 130, Folder 23)
        - CCA UN/ESCAP: Proposals and reports, 1997 (Box 130, Folder 24)
        - CCA UN/ESCAP: Reports, finance consultations, 1997 (Box 131, Folder 1)
        - CCA-URM Staff monthly reports, 1991-1992 (Box 131, Folder 2)
        - Climate Change, incl. sharing paper by Prawate Khidarn, 1995-1996 (Box 131, Folder 3)
        - Climate Change, 1996-2000 (Box 131, Folder 4)
        - Development and Service Programme Committee meeting minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 131, Folder 5)
        - Development and Service Programme Committee meeting minutes, 1982, 1986 (Box 131, Folder 6)
        - Development and Service Project file, 1981-1983 (Box 131, Folder 7)
        - D, 1994-1997 (Box 131, Folder 8)
        - Disabled persons, incl. stories of CCA Assembly participants, 1989-1990 (Box 131, Folder 9)
        - Documentation for Action Groups in Asia (DAGA), 1988 (Box 131, Folder 10)
        - EACC/CCA papers and correspondence, including "The Development Challenge and the Churches in E. Asia," EACC Committee on Development, 1969-1976 (Box 131, Folder 11)
        - EACC/CCA papers reports re. healthier medical concerns, 1969, 1976 (Box 131, Folder 12)
        - EACC Committee on Christian Medical Work, 1970, 1972, 1976 (Box 131, Folder 13)
        - EACC Program for Justice Service, no date (Box 131, Folder 14)
        - EACC - Sodapex project in Asia, 1971-1972 (Box 131, Folder 15)
        - EACC Strategy for Development Concerns, 1972 (Box 131, Folder 16)
        - Ecumenical Coalition on Third World Tourism incl. auditors' report, "Alternative Tourism" resource book (1 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box 131, Folder 17)
        - Ecumenical Coalition on Third World Tourism incl. auditors' report, "Alternative Tourism" resource book (2 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box 131, Folder 18)
        - Ecumenical Coalition on Third World Tourism, papers and correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 131, Folder 19)
        - Ecumenical Coalition on Third World Tourism incl. Executive Committee materials and auditors' report, 1986-1987 (Box 131, Folder 20)
        - Intensive Training Exchange Program, 1996-2001 (Box 131, Folder 21)
        - Yong Bock Kim "Reflections on Peoples Rights in Asia," excerpts from "Challenge of World Poverty", 1970 (Box 131, Folder 22)
        - Mekong Concerns, 1998-2000 (Box 131, Folder 23)
        - Miscellaneous papers and travel reports, 1993-1995 (Box 132, Folder 1)
        - MRAI reports, correspondence, and collected materials (1 of 2), 1994-2000 (Box 132, Folder 2)
        - MRAI reports, correspondence, and collected materials (2 of 2), 1994-2000 (Box 132, Folder 3)
        - Program Committee on Development and Service Working Group incl. program reports, 1986-1987 (Box 132, Folder 4)
        - Program Committee review, 1996 (Box 179, Folder 22)
        - Project: "Training on Community based Savings and Credit" no. 970034, 1997-1999 (Box 132, Folder 5)
      - Development Fund
        - Correspondence re. Development Programme Fund, 1978-1987 (Box 132, Folder 8)
        - Correspondence re. Development Assistance Fund (1 of 2), 1980 (Box 132, Folder 9)
        - Correspondence re. Development Assistance Fund (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 132, Folder 10)
        - Correspondence re. Development project requests, 1980-1985 (Box 132, Folder 11)
        - Correspondence re. Development Programme Fund Projects (1 of 3), 1983-1984 (Box 132, Folder 12)
        - Correspondence re. Development Programme Fund Projects (2 of 3), 1983-1984 (Box 132, Folder 13)
        - Correspondence re. Development Programme Fund Projects (3 of 3), 1983-1984 (Box 132, Folder 14)
        - Correspondence re. Development Programme Fund (1 of 2), 1983-1987 (Box 132, Folder 15)
        - Correspondence re. Development Programme Fund (2 of 2), 1983-1987 (Box 132, Folder 16)
        - Correspondence re. Development Programme Fund, 1984 (Box 132, Folder 17)
        - Correspondence re. Development Programme Fund, 1985-1986 (Box 132, Folder 18)
        - Correspondence re. Development Programme Fund, 1986-1989 (Box 133, Folder 1)
        - Correspondence re. Development Programme Fund, 1987-1989 (Box 133, Folder 2)
        - Correspondence re. Development Programme Fund, 1990 (Box 133, Folder 3)
        - Correspondence re. Development Programme Fund, 1991-1993 (Box 133, Folder 4)
        - Correspondence re. Development Programme Fund project proposals, 1995 (Box 133, Folder 5)
        - Correspondence re. Development Programme Fund project proposals, 1996 (Box 133, Folder 6)
        - Correspondence re. Development Programme Fund project proposals, 1997 (Box 133, Folder 7)
        - Correspondence re. Development Programme Fund project proposals, 1998 (Box 133, Folder 8)
        - Development Fund Projects (1 of 2), 1998-1999 (Box 133, Folder 9)
        - Development Fund Projects (2 of 2), 1998-1999 (Box 133, Folder 10)
        - Development Programme Fund project proposals, 1999 (Box 133, Folder 11)
      - Indochina
        - Cambodia reports incl. Bible study by Harvey Perkins, 1993 (Box 133, Folder 12)
        - Correspondence, Indochina Advisory Group, 1987 (Box 133, Folder 13)
        - Correspondence, Indochina Roundtable, 1989 (Box 133, Folder 14)
        - Correspondence, Indochina Roundtable, 1990 (Box 133, Folder 15)
        - Correspondence re. Indochina (incl. reports), 1987-1988 (Box 133, Folder 16)
        - Correspondence re. Indochina (incl. reports), 1989-1990 (Box 133, Folder 17)
        - Correspondence re. Indochina, 1989-1993 (Box 134, Folder 1)
        - Correspondence re. Indochina (incl. reports), 1991-1992 (Box 134, Folder 2)
        - Correspondence re. Indochina, 1991-1993 (Box 134, Folder 3)
        - Correspondence re. Indochina, 1993 (Box 134, Folder 4)
        - Correspondence re. Indochina, Cambodia visitation incl. reports, 1992-1993 (Box 134, Folder 5)
        - Correspondence re. Indochina, Vietnam meeting, 1992-1993 (Box 134, Folder 6)
        - Correspondence re. Laos Program, 1988-1989 (Box 134, Folder 7)
        - Correspondence re. Laos Program, 1990-1995 (Box 134, Folder 8)
        - Indochina Concerns: Cambodia CEC, CWS, CCWA reports, finance, and correspondence (1 of 3), 1994-1999 (Box 134, Folder 9)
        - Indochina Concerns: Cambodia CEC, CWS, CCWA reports, finance, and correspondence (2 of 3), 1994-1999 (Box 134, Folder 10)
        - Indochina Concerns: Cambodia CEC, CWS, CCWA reports, finance, and correspondence (3 of 3), 1994-1999 (Box 134, Folder 11)
        - Indochina Concerns: Cambodia Christian Women's Association, 1995-2000 (Box 134, Folder 12)
        - Indochina Concerns: "Ecumenical Presence and Ecumenical Programs in Cambodia", 1991 January (Box 134, Folder 13)
        - Indochina Consortium, circular letters, correspondence, news clippings incl. Stephen Webb notebook (1 of 2), 1982-1984 (Box 134, Folder 14)
        - Indochina Consortium, circular letters, correspondence, news clippings incl. Stephen Webb notebook (2 of 2), 1982-1984 (Box 134, Folder 15)
        - Indochina Consortium, reports and collected material, 1982 (Box 134, Folder 16)
        - Indochina papers and correspondence, 1975-1979 (Box 134, Folder 17)
        - Indochina papers and correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 135, Folder 1)
        - Indochina papers and correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 135, Folder 2)
        - Indochina papers, reports and correspondence (1 of 2), 1994-1996 (Box 135, Folder 3)
        - Indochina papers, reports and correspondence (2 of 2), 1994-1996 (Box 135, Folder 4)
        - Indochina, proposals on CCA role in Indochina and refugees by Peter Holden, 1994 (Box 135, Folder 5)
        - Kampong Thom Project Meeting, 1994-1996 (Box 135, Folder 6)
        - Laos government accord, projects and agreements re. staff from abroad, 1968-1976 (Box 160, Folder 29)
        - Pastoral Solidarity visit to Indonesia, 1999 (Box 135, Folder 7)
        - Refugees in Indochina (1 of 2), 1976-1982 (Box 160, Folder 26)
        - Refugees in Indochina (2 of 2), 1976-1982 (Box 160, Folder 27)
        - Vietnam, 1976-1979 (Box 160, Folder 28)
        - VLC incl. reports and VLC Update newsletters, 1994-1996 (Box 135, Folder 8)
        - VLC: Cambodia papers and correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 135, Folder 9)
        - VLC Core Group Meeting, Phnom Penh, Cambodia, 1993 (Box 135, Folder 10)
        - VLC Core Group Meeting, New York, 1994 (Box 135, Folder 11)
        - VLC Core Group Meeting, Hong Kong, 1994 (Box 135, Folder 12)
        - VLC Core Group Meeting, Geneva, 1995 (Box 135, Folder 13)
        - VLC Core Group Meeting, Hong Kong, 1996 (Box 135, Folder 14)
        - VLC Core Group Meeting, Geneva, 1998 (Box 135, Folder 15)
        - VLC Core Group Meeting, New York, 1998 (Box 135, Folder 16)
        - VLC Core Group Meeting, Hong Kong, 1999 (Box 135, Folder 17)
        - VLC Indochina Forum Meeting, Bangkok, 1993 (Box 135, Folder 18)
        - VLC Indochina Forum Meeting, Bangkok, 1995 (Box 135, Folder 19)
        - VLC: Laos papers and correspondence, 1993-1997 (Box 135, Folder 20)
        - VLC: Miscellaneous papers, no date (Box 135, Folder 21)
        - VLC: Kampuchea papers and correspondence (1 of 2), 1981-1984 (Box 135, Folder 22)
        - VLC: Kampuchea papers and correspondence (2 of 2), 1981-1984 (Box 135, Folder 23)
        - VLC: Vietnam papers and correspondence, 1994-1999 (Box 135, Folder 24)
        - VLC Working Group Meeting, Bangkok, 1996 (Box 135, Folder 25)
        - VLK Task Group, 1968-1984 (Box 135, Folder 26)
        - VLK Task Group meeting minutes, 1978 (Box 135, Folder 27)
    - Collected material
      - Collected papers and articles
        - Asian Countries, readings B-I (Burma-India), includes Clement John, 1976-1993 (Box 136, Folder 1)
        - Asian Countries, readings I-P (India-Philippines), includes Clement John, 1976-1993 (Box 136, Folder 2)
        - Asian Countries: readings R-V (Sri Lanka-Vietnam), includes Clement John, 1976-1993 (Box 136, Folder 3)
        - Christian medical programs in Asia, reports and country papers, 1967-1972 (Box 136, Folder 4)
        - Church World Service: News clippings re. Cambodia, 1994 January-March (Box 136, Folder 5)
        - Church World Service: News clippings re. Cambodia, 1994 March-April (Box 136, Folder 6)
        - Church World Service: News clippings re. Cambodia, 1994 April-June (Box 136, Folder 7)
        - Church World Service: News clippings re. Cambodia, 1994 June-August (Box 136, Folder 8)
        - Church World Service: News clippings re. Cambodia, 1994 August-September (Box 136, Folder 9)
        - Church World Service: News clippings re. Cambodia, 1994 September-October (Box 136, Folder 10)
        - Church World Service: News clippings re. Cambodia, 1994 November-December (Box 136, Folder 11)
        - Collected papers, Defense resources and violence in politics, 1977-1987 (Box 136, Folder 12)
        - Collected papers, Nuclearization, 1983-1988 (Box 136, Folder 13)
        - Collected papers, Towards Justice and Peace, 1978-1989 (Box 136, Folder 14)
        - Collected papers, US Intervention in TW countries; Conflicts in Asian countries, 1975-1980 (Box 136, Folder 15)
        - Collected papers, the U.S. policy, 1977-1980 (Box 136, Folder 16)
        - Charles Elliott "Development Debate", 1971 (Box 137, Folder 1)
        - Fight Back legal resource manual published by Kia Mohio Kia Marama Trust (1 of 2), 1983 (Box 137, Folder 2)
        - Fight Back legal resource manual published by Kia Mohio Kia Marama Trust (2 of 2, 1983 (Box 137, Folder 3)
        - Health, miscellaneous papers, 1970-1976 (Box 137, Folder 4)
        - Peter Hollingworth "Violence, Non-violence and Social Justice", 1976 March (Box 137, Folder 5)
        - Human rights, national reports, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 6)
        - Report: Ecumenical Training Course for International Solidarity Work, no date (Box 137, Folder 7)
        - Sodapex papers and reports, 1972-1975 (Box 137, Folder 8)
        - UN Summaries of the Jackson Report, Pearson Report, Tinbergen Report, no date (Box 137, Folder 9)
      - Country Files
        - Australia papers and collected material, 1976 (Box 137, Folder 10)
        - Bangladesh papers and collected material (1 of 2), 1974-1976 (Box 137, Folder 11)
        - Bangladesh papers and collected material (2 of 2), 1974-1976 (Box 137, Folder 12)
        - Bangladesh, Christian Commission for Development papers, 1974-1976 (Box 137, Folder 13)
        - Burma papers and collected material, 1975-1976 (Box 137, Folder 14)
        - Burma, "Dawn News Bulletin" and new clippings, 1989-1991 (Box 137, Folder 15)
        - Hong Kong papers and collected material, 1975-1976 (Box 137, Folder 16)
        - India papers and collected material, 1974-1976 (Box 137, Folder 17)
        - India re. Dalit population, 1993 (Box 137, Folder 18)
        - Indonesia papers and collected material, 1975-1977 (Box 137, Folder 19)
        - Indonesia, WCC/CCA reports and collected Parpen newspaper clippings, 1987-1993 (Box 137, Folder 20)
        - Japan - Koreans in Japan, 1974 (Box 137, Folder 21)
        - Pakistan papers and collected material (1 of 2), 1971 (Box 137, Folder 22)
        - Pakistan papers and collected material (2 of 2), 1971 (Box 137, Folder 23)
        - Philippines papers and collected material, 1976-1977 (Box 137, Folder 24)
        - Sri Lanka papers and collected material, 1974-1977 (Box 138, Folder 1)
        - Taiwan papers and collected material, 1973-1979 (Box 138, Folder 2)
        - Taiwan papers and collected material, 1993-1994 (Box 138, Folder 3)
        - Thailand papers and collected material, 1964-1972 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Program Activities and Conferences
      - Asia Alliance YMCAs Executive Committee Meeting, Hong Kong, 1995 (Box 138, Folder 5)
      - Asia Mission Conference - Planning Materials, Cipanas Ciantur, Indonesia, 1989 (Box 138, Folder 6)
      - Asian Non-Asian Churches' Involvement in Indochina, 2-6 June 1996, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia (Box 138, Folder 7)
      - Asian Church Leaders' Conference, 8-11 March 1995, Phnom Penh, Cambodia (Box 138, Folder 8)
      - Asian Cultural Forum on Development, 1987-1992 (Box 138, Folder 9)
      - Asian Ecumenical Conference for Development, Tokyo, Japan (1 of 4), 1970 (Box 138, Folder 10)
      - Asian Ecumenical Conference for Development, Tokyo, Japan (2 of 4), 1970 (Box 138, Folder 11)
      - Asian Ecumenical Conference for Development, Tokyo, Japan (3 of 4), 1970 (Box 138, Folder 12)
      - Asian Ecumenical Conference for Development, Tokyo, Japan (4 of 4), 1970 (Box 138, Folder 13)
      - CCA and Ecumenical Partners Meeting, Hong Kong, 1994 (Box 138, Folder 14)
      - CCA Consultation on Globalism and its Impact on Human Rights, Bangalore, 1998 (Box 138, Folder 15)
      - CCA Program Committee Meeting, Singapore, 1986 (Box 138, Folder 16)
      - CCA Staff Meeting, Chiang Mai, 1989 (Box 138, Folder 17)
      - CCA Staff Meeting, Hong Kong, 1988 (Box 138, Folder 18)
      - CCA Task Group on Churches' Concern for East Timor, 8-9 Oct. 1997, Hong Kong (Box 138, Folder 19)
      - CCA/WCC Roundtable meeting on Ecumenical Response to Indonesia and East Timor, 1999 November (Box 138, Folder 20)
      - CCA/WCC Workshop on Internally Displaced Communities, May 15-21, 1996 (Box 138, Folder 21)
      - CCA-CCM Workshop on Disability Concerns, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia, 1993 (Box 139, Folder 1)
      - CCA-CMC Consultation on Health Concerns, Singapore, 1987 (Box 139, Folder 2)
      - CCA-ICCO Meeting, Utrecht, Netherlands, 1976 (Box 139, Folder 3)
      - CCA-NCC D, 1996 (Box 139, Folder 4)
      - CCA-WCC Consultation on Health Concerns, Singapore, 1987 (Box 139, Folder 5)
      - CCA-WCC Development Forum, Singapore (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 139, Folder 6)
      - CCA-WCC Development Forum, Singapore (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 139, Folder 7)
      - Community Health Workshop, Indonesia (1 of 2), 1983 (Box 139, Folder 8)
      - Community Health Workshop, Indonesia (2 of 2), 1983 (Box 139, Folder 9)
      - Community Motivation Training Workshop, Jakarta, Indonesia: Correspondence and Report, 1976 (Box 139, Folder 10)
      - Consultation on a Regional Service and Development Strategy for Asia, Bangkok, Thailand, 1973 (Box 139, Folder 11)
      - Consultation on Emerging Trends in Indochina, Phnom Penh, Cambodia, 1994 March 24-26 (Box 139, Folder 12)
      - Consultation on Gender and Development in Asia, October 19-25, 1994 (Box 139, Folder 13)
      - Consultation on Rethinking Tourism, Bali, 1994 (Box 139, Folder 14)
      - Consultative Committee for Coordination of Aid to Kampuchea meeting, 1979 (Box 139, Folder 15)
      - Development Education Strategies Workshop, Singapore, 1980 (Box 139, Folder 16)
      - Development Guidelines Workshop, Philippines, 1979 (Box 139, Folder 17)
      - Development Management Training, Thailand (1 of 2), 1999 (Box 139, Folder 18)
      - Development Management Training, Thailand (2 of 2), 1999 (Box 139, Folder 19)
      - Ecology and Development Workshop - Church's Response to Environment, Sukabumi, Indonesia, 1995 (Box 140, Folder 1)
      - Economic and Social Commission for Asia and the Pacific (UN ESCAP), 1997-1999 (Box 140, Folder 2)
      - ESP Workshop and Evaluation on Scolarship Programme, Yogyakaarta, Indonesia, 1995 (Box 140, Folder 3)
      - Exchange Program for Disabled Persons, 1992 (Box 140, Folder 4)
      - Exploratory Inter-Religious Meeting on Justic and Development in Asia, Bangkok, 1973 (Box 140, Folder 5)
      - Exploratory Meeting on Trade, Economic Justice in Asia, Bangkok, 1973 (Box 140, Folder 6)
      - Facilitators' Training for Healing Ministry (South Asia), Bangladesh, 1999 (Box 140, Folder 7)
      - Facilitators' Training for Healing Ministry, Chiang Mai, Thailand, 1994 (Box 140, Folder 8)
      - Food and Hunger Crisis, Bangalore, India - Report of the two day consultation, 1975 (Box 140, Folder 9)
      - Gender and Awareness Workshop; Development Management Training, 1999 (Box 140, Folder 10)
      - Gender Awareness and Sensitivity Course: Women in Inclusive Community, 1997 (Box 140, Folder 11)
      - Intensive Training and Exchange Program, Chiang Mai, Thailand, 1995 (Box 140, Folder 12)
      - Intensive Training and Exchange Program, Sri Lanka, 1996 (Box 140, Folder 13)
      - Intensive Training and Exchange Program, Thailand, 1997 (Box 140, Folder 14)
      - International Workshop on Tourism, Philippines (1 of 2), 1980 (Box 140, Folder 15)
      - International Workshop on Tourism, Philippines (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 140, Folder 16)
      - Mini Consultation on "Church and the Disabled People in Asia" Singapore, 1987 (Box 140, Folder 17)
      - Peace Security in Indochina in the Emerging Political, Economic, and Security Alliance Context in Southeast Asia, 9-12 April 1997, Hong Kong (Box 140, Folder 18)
      - Programme Activities incl. summary reports (1 of 3), 1997 (Box 141, Folder 1)
      - Programme Activities incl. summary reports (2 of 3), 1997 (Box 141, Folder 2)
      - Programme Activities incl. summary reports (3 of 3), 1997 (Box 141, Folder 3)
      - Programme Activities incl. summary reports, 1997-2000 (Box 141, Folder 4)
      - Programme Activities incl. summary reports (1 of 3), 1998 (Box 141, Folder 5)
      - Programme Activities incl. summary reports (2 of 3), 1998 (Box 141, Folder 6)
      - Programme Activities incl. summary reports (3 of 3), 1998 (Box 141, Folder 7)
      - Programme Activities incl. meeting sharing papers and correspondence (1 of 4), 1998 (Box 141, Folder 8)
      - Programme Activities incl. meeting sharing papers and correspondence (2 of 4), 1998 (Box 141, Folder 9)